When modeling, sometimes there is no gap, we can flexibly use the fixed needle and the selection grid tool to deal with it.
When modeling, if you look at the surface of the濃密紋理, you will not be able to see the unstable place.
When the surface of the濃密紋理 is opened, the surface will show the thickness of the application, and the positive and negative sides will appear at the same time.
After switching from the 3D window to the vertical line in the menu bar, the back of the clothing will be displayed as a dark area to distinguish the positive and negative.
Now look at the sleeve side, you will see that there is a problem with the positive and negative differences in the grid.
The part of the sleeve that is rolled up is the back side.
If you use the selection grid tool, you can pull out the part that goes in.
When selecting the selection grid tool, the first three are selection grid tools, the difference is that their shapes are different.
Here we choose the selection grid comparison tool, which is convenient to directly select a whole grid.
When dragging the selection frame to the frame selection grid in the 3D window,
it is selected according to the current perspective, so you can not select the grid that is blocked.
We can use this as a position positioning, and then select the grid in the 2D window.
After selecting, you can go back to the 3D window to select the grid and pull them out, and then pull out the other parts as well.
When pulling, the positioning ball I use is the world coordinate.
You can adjust the coordinate type according to your needs.
In the 3D window, you can select the coordinate type by right-clicking.
When selecting the screen coordinate, the positioning ball is based on the perspective of the lens.
If you select the segment coordinate, the positioning ball is the original coordinate based on the selected object.
This coordinate is mainly used on objects that are inserted externally, such as virtual models, objects with their own coordinates.
Then gradually pull out the broken grid.
When all the grid below the fold line is pulled out, start simulation.
If you can't fold the whole thing out quickly, you can print the board.
After simulation, finish printing and start dealing with the skirt part.
You can see that the skirt part now has a problem of irregular folding.
When dealing with this part, we can use the fixed pin tool.
There are also two types of fixed pins.
First, freeze the other boards so that they will not simulate when they are in contact.
Now come to the place where the folding is irregular.
In the 3D window, click on the board.
A blue support point will appear in the 2D window.
As a reference, we can see that the inner line near this point is red.
This means that this line uses a fold angle less than 180 degrees.
It should be prominent on the front of the board.
But now the fold angle is 360 degrees, but the line is outside.
The 0 degree line is folded to the inside.
This is wrong.
So we need to use the fixed pin to pull out the grid hidden inside.
Select a small part of the grid along the line hidden in the back.
Do not select too much, otherwise it may not be stable when it is turned out.
Then pull this edge out and start simulation.
Different from the selected grid, the fixed pin will be fixed in the 3D window.
So it can better maintain the position of this edge.
After stabilizing, delete the fixed pin and then start simulation.
If you use the selected grid to select, although it can achieve the same effect.
But after opening the simulation, the selected grid will not remain in the set position.
So sometimes there are unstable times.
When you switch the tool or click on other positions, the selected grid will cancel the selection.
Therefore, it is recommended to use the fixed pin tool to deal with the fold angle pile type of foldable pile.
When dealing with the rest of the part,
because it is a whole board,
you can add a whole piece of fixed pin to the board on the front side to prevent the board from transforming.
In this way, the front part will no longer be unstable.
Double-click the inner line to select a line and add a fixed pin.
Then move out.
Double-click the inner line to select a line and add a fixed pin to the board.
After simulation,
remove the fixed pin and simulate again.
Then check control is finished.
How to fix an gratitude velvety thread
First, put on the scene of the graduated student.
Open the viewport,
the background,
and the menu in which it is contained.
Take a look,
here we can print the pattern,